

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Eindhoven, the Netherlands

□ (+31) 6 4820 9406 | 🗷 cas@eliens.co | 🖸 cascer1 | 🖹 cas-eliëns | 🛅 caseliens | 🚭 cascer1

"Truth can only be found in one place: the code."

Summary _

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history in backend development.

Skilled in Java, PHP, Deployment, and Customer Service. Strong software professional with a Bachelor of Information & Communication Technology focused in Computer Software Engineering and Cyber Security from Fontys Hogescholen.

Experience _____

ISAAC Eindhoven, NL

Developer Sep 2018 - Current

• Develop Java API back-end for financial applications

Sharegroup b.v.

SOFTWARE ARCHITECT & LEAD BACK-END DEVELOPER

Dec 2017 - Current

• Develop API back-end for Soundshare platform

Duco HostingEindhoven, NL

Owner Apr 2013 - Jun 2018

- Managed hosting infrastructure and servers
- Linux server security and configuration
- Managed DNS and other domain configurations

ISAAC Eindhoven, NL

INTERN JAVA DEVELOPMENT Aug 2016 - Jan 2017

- Developed automated API documentation tooling for RAML and Swagger
- Researched iDin authentication for secure financial logins

HEMA Eindhoven, NL

Sales Representative Nov 2010 - Aug 2018

- Maintain proper stocking levels for internal consumables like receipt paper and office supplies
- · Applied and maintained in-store promotional material

Education ____

Fontys Hogeschool ICT Eindhoven, the Netherlands

 SOFTWARE ENGINEERING
 2014 - 2018

- Completed courses toward a bachelor in Software Engineering
- Participated in the Fontys ICT Delta excellence program

Extracurricular Activity _____

Cas Eliëns · Résumé

reddit.com/r/diabetes online

COMMUNITY MODERATOR May 2017 - current

- Moderate popular chat platform for a diabetes support group.
- Provide helpful insights and support in diabetes care.
- Moderate the r/diabetes community on Reddit.
- Help protect the community from unwelcome content.

Writing.

Why every diabetic should switch to a closed-loop system

medium.com/@cas.eliens/bd520c732dc1

Apr 2018

- WRITER

 Describe advantages of automation in diabetes management
- Give real-life examples of automation results in diabetes management